[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donny"]}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "How are you, sir?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", ",", "sir", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Good to see you, Donny.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "to", "see", "you", ",", "Donny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "First up, how are you feeling?", "question_tokens": ["First", "up", ",", "how", "are", "you", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Feel great.", "answer_tokens": ["Feel", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["99 percent"]}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "What is -- give me the heart -- take me through a day in the life and happening, just what it is to live with this stuff?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "--", "give", "me", "the", "heart", "--", "take", "me", "through", "a", "day", "in", "the", "life", "and", "happening", ",", "just", "what", "it", "is", "to", "live", "with", "this", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", ":", "JJ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", ",", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Well, I mean, the largest part of the day, 99 percent of the day, is the same as everybody else's day.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "the", "largest", "part", "of", "the", "day", ",", "99", "percent", "of", "the", "day", ",", "is", "the", "same", "as", "everybody", "else", "'s", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "Tracy runs the show, right?", "question_tokens": ["Tracy", "runs", "the", "show", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Tracy is the CEO (ph).", "answer_tokens": ["Tracy", "is", "the", "CEO", "(", "ph", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "You're on -- are you on drugs right now, as we speak?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "on", "--", "are", "you", "on", "drugs", "right", "now", ",", "as", "we", "speak", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "I'm on all kinds of drugs.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "on", "all", "kinds", "of", "drugs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "He gets in, how does your life get affected?", "question_tokens": ["He", "gets", "in", ",", "how", "does", "your", "life", "get", "affected", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Well, I mean, he's spoken out against science.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "he", "'s", "spoken", "out", "against", "science", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "You did get the job, didn't you, because you really didn't sing it that well?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "get", "the", "job", ",", "did", "n't", "you", ",", "because", "you", "really", "did", "n't", "sing", "it", "that", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "I got the job.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "the", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Would he still be a Republican?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "he", "still", "be", "a", "Republican", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "You know, I always say he would be converted to being a Democrat now or be in jail.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "always", "say", "he", "would", "be", "converted", "to", "being", "a", "Democrat", "now", "or", "be", "in", "jail", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Drexel Burnham"]}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "(INAUDIBLE) insider trading?", "question_tokens": ["(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "insider", "trading", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Yes, back in the days of Drexel Burnham.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "back", "in", "the", "days", "of", "Drexel", "Burnham", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "I sing like Mitt Romney, you notice that?", "question_tokens": ["I", "sing", "like", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "you", "notice", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Yes, I do, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", ",", "RB", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Such as?", "question_tokens": ["Such", "as", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "I think -- I think there's some issues around Gitmo and privacy and some other things like that that I thought -- I thought would be handled by now, just things that can mess around the edges that I thought might have been cleaned up and just from an idealistic point of view.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "some", "issues", "around", "Gitmo", "and", "privacy", "and", "some", "other", "things", "like", "that", "that", "I", "thought", "--", "I", "thought", "would", "be", "handled", "by", "now", ",", "just", "things", "that", "can", "mess", "around", "the", "edges", "that", "I", "thought", "might", "have", "been", "cleaned", "up", "and", "just", "from", "an", "idealistic", "point", "of", "view", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Has he done enough on stem cell?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "done", "enough", "on", "stem", "cell", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "I'm not a surrogate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "a", "surrogate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "What happens then?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happens", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Well, we can't fund that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "ca", "n't", "fund", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "You hid it at the beginning.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "hid", "it", "at", "the", "beginning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "VB", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "What would you say if there's a young person out there, and just yesterday they found out they have Parkinson's, what would you say to them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "if", "there", "'s", "a", "young", "person", "out", "there", ",", "and", "just", "yesterday", "they", "found", "out", "they", "have", "Parkinson", "'s", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "EX", ",", "CC", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "POS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Just don't let -- don't let others project onto you what you're experiencing.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "do", "n't", "let", "--", "do", "n't", "let", "others", "project", "onto", "you", "what", "you", "'re", "experiencing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "JJ", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Can I get you a soda or something, Larry?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "get", "you", "a", "soda", "or", "something", ",", "Larry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Sure, that'd be great.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "that", "'d", "be", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Did you shake that up on purpose?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "shake", "that", "up", "on", "purpose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Parkinson's.", "answer_tokens": ["Parkinson", "'s", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "When Larry called you, what did he say, let's do Parkinson's?", "question_tokens": ["When", "Larry", "called", "you", ",", "what", "did", "he", "say", ",", "let", "'s", "do", "Parkinson", "'s", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VB", "POS", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Yes, it was great.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "was", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "EUTSCH: So in that scene, it's basically, OK, you're going to shake up the Coke, spill it on me, other than that, it's just go and you guys (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_tokens": ["EUTSCH", ":", "So", "in", "that", "scene", ",", "it", "'s", "basically", ",", "OK", ",", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "shake", "up", "the", "Coke", ",", "spill", "it", "on", "me", ",", "other", "than", "that", ",", "it", "'s", "just", "go", "and", "you", "guys", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NNP", ":", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Coke"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "You guys know what you're doing there, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "guys", "know", "what", "you", "'re", "doing", "there", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "He -- well, he's brilliant.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "--", "well", ",", "he", "'s", "brilliant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "So we're cool?", "question_tokens": ["So", "we", "'re", "cool", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "We will be cool in about seven minutes.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "will", "be", "cool", "in", "about", "seven", "minutes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "Can you come back in like a minute, give us a minute?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "come", "back", "in", "like", "a", "minute", ",", "give", "us", "a", "minute", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "I'd like six minutes and 31 seconds.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "like", "six", "minutes", "and", "31", "seconds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Forget whatever the physical challenges, is there a role that's not going to turn you on that somehow doesn't move the needle for disability or for Parkinson's?", "question_tokens": ["Forget", "whatever", "the", "physical", "challenges", ",", "is", "there", "a", "role", "that", "'s", "not", "going", "to", "turn", "you", "on", "that", "somehow", "does", "n't", "move", "the", "needle", "for", "disability", "or", "for", "Parkinson", "'s", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "OX: Yes, I mean, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["OX", ":", "Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Ann?", "question_tokens": ["Ann", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "I always think the camera can tell.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "always", "think", "the", "camera", "can", "tell", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "You do?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "First time they tell you at 25, what goes through your head?", "question_tokens": ["First", "time", "they", "tell", "you", "at", "25", ",", "what", "goes", "through", "your", "head", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "CD", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "Well, I didn't freak out because I knew nothing about the illness.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "freak", "out", "because", "I", "knew", "nothing", "about", "the", "illness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "What is the key?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "key", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "There's no hierarchy of suffering.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "no", "hierarchy", "of", "suffering", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "So why would they?", "question_tokens": ["So", "why", "would", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "EUTSCH: We're going to take a break, guys.", "answer_tokens": ["EUTSCH", ":", "We", "'re", "going", "to", "take", "a", "break", ",", "guys", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "What's the secret, seriously, all kidding aside?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "secret", ",", "seriously", ",", "all", "kidding", "aside", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "I think a sense of humor, flexibility and the ability to walk away.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "a", "sense", "of", "humor", ",", "flexibility", "and", "the", "ability", "to", "walk", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "What the heck does that mean?", "question_tokens": ["What", "the", "heck", "does", "that", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "I don't mean -- I mean walk away from bad moments.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "mean", "--", "I", "mean", "walk", "away", "from", "bad", "moments", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "Does that help you in your own?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "help", "you", "in", "your", "own", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "No, we don't have enough time to help me.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "have", "enough", "time", "to", "help", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "You see that ad, forget politics aside, what is your reaction, just from getting somebody elected?", "question_tokens": ["You", "see", "that", "ad", ",", "forget", "politics", "aside", ",", "what", "is", "your", "reaction", ",", "just", "from", "getting", "somebody", "elected", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "Planned Parenthood for the Christian right is a symbol.", "answer_tokens": ["Planned", "Parenthood", "for", "the", "Christian", "right", "is", "a", "symbol", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "They can't win this way?", "question_tokens": ["They", "ca", "n't", "win", "this", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "I agree with you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "agree", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "But is it going to come back to bite them?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "it", "going", "to", "come", "back", "to", "bite", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "I have never seen the Republican party dragged this far to the right in the primary process.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "never", "seen", "the", "Republican", "party", "dragged", "this", "far", "to", "the", "right", "in", "the", "primary", "process", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "Have you seen anything like this?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "seen", "anything", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "To this extent, no.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "this", "extent", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["30 billion dollars"], "LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"], "ORGANIZATION": ["NIH"]}, "docId": "120314pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "CD", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "So as somebody who obviously wants everything to be cured, but M.S. is clearly going to be first on your list, how do you come to terms with that?", "question_tokens": ["So", "as", "somebody", "who", "obviously", "wants", "everything", "to", "be", "cured", ",", "but", "M.S.", "is", "clearly", "going", "to", "be", "first", "on", "your", "list", ",", "how", "do", "you", "come", "to", "terms", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "The NIH budget is frozen at about 30 billion dollars, which pays for about 2.5 months in Afghanistan.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "NIH", "budget", "is", "frozen", "at", "about", "30", "billion", "dollars", ",", "which", "pays", "for", "about", "2.5", "months", "in", "Afghanistan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["M.S."]}}]